Stewart L. Udall papers, 1950-2010
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Series VIII: Recent Additions to the Collection, 1940-2010
  - Radiation Files, 1978-1993
    - Radiation Files: Stewart Udall’s Journal. 1978-1979 (Box 244, Folder 3)
    - Radiation Files: Radiation Fallout Cases. 1978-1982 (Box 244, Folder 4)
    - Radiation Files: Navajo Cases. 1979-1983 (Box 244, Folder 5)
    - Radiation Files: Navajo Uranium Miners versus U.S. Newspaper Clippings. (Box 244, Folder 6)
    - Radiation Files: Fallout Sheep Case Papers. 1979-1985 (Box 244, Folder 7)
    - Radiation Files: Stewart Udall Lobbying for the Radiation Exposure Act. 1990-1993 (Box 244, Folder 8)
    - Radiation Files: Fact Brief-Begay versus the U.S. and Begay versus Kerr-Magee Corporation. (Box 244, Folder 9)
  - Photograph and Awards, 1905-1992
    The photographs are arranged by decade. The Awards and Oversized Photographs are arranged by size.
    - Photographs and Awards: Photographs. 1950s (Box 245, Folder 1)
    - Photographs and Awards: Photographs. 1960s (Box 245, Folder 2)
    - Photographs and Awards: Photographs. 1960s (Box 245, Folder 3)
    - Photographs and Awards: Photographs. 1960s (Box 245, Folder 4)
    - Photographs and Awards: Photographs. Signing of the National Trails Bill. September 1968 (Box 245, Folder 5)
    - Photographs and Awards: Photographs. Signing of Central Arizona Project. September 1968 (Box 245, Folder 6)
    - Photographs and Awards: Photographs. 1970s (Box 245, Folder 7)
    - Photographs and Awards: Photographs. 1980s (Box 245, Folder 8)
    - Photographs and Awards: Photographs. 1990s (Box 245, Folder 9)
    - Photographs and Awards: Photographs. Lee Udall: Center for Arts of Indian America. (Box 245, Folder 10)
    - Photographs and Awards: Miscellaneous, Certificates of Election to Central Arizona Water Conservation Board. 1980 & 1982 (Box 246, Folder 1)
    - Photographs and Awards: Miscellaneous, Birthday Greetings from President Lyndon Johnson and Ladybird Johnson. 1963 (Box 246, Folder 2)
    - Photographs and Awards: Awards and Miscellaneous, Certificate of Knighthood from the King of Spain. 1988 (Box 246, Folder 3)
    - Photographs and Awards: Awards and Miscellaneous, Gaspar Perez de Villagra Award Presented to Stewart Udall for His Book To The Inland Empire. (Box 246, Folder 4)
    - Photographs and Awards: Awards and Miscellaneous, Certificate of Arizona Parks Task Force. 1981 (Box 246, Folder 5)
    - Photographs and Awards: Awards and Miscellaneous, Honorary Degree from Fairleigh Dickinson University. (Box 246, Folder 6)
    - Photographs and Awards: Awards and Miscellaneous, Christmas Card from President Lyndon Johnson and Ladybird Johnson, 1966. 1966 (Box 246, Folder 7)
    - Photographs and Awards: Awards and Miscellaneous, Honorary degree from the University of Massachusetts. 1992 (Box 246, Folder 8)
    - Oversized Materials: Photographs and Posters, Photograph Delaware River Basin Commission Meeting. March 1968 (Box 247, Folder 1)
    - Oversized Materials: Photographs and Posters, Photograph Arizona Congressional Delegation and Governor. 1961 (Box 247, Folder 2)
    - Oversized Materials: Photographs and Posters, Photograph President Kennedy First Days in Office. February 1961 (Box 247, Folder 3)
    - Oversized Materials: Photographs and Posters, Photograph Climb up Mount Fuji, Japan. 1961 (Box 247, Folder 4)
    - Oversized Materials: Photographs and Posters, Photograph Cabinet Mmembers before Meeting (Freeman, Douglas, Dillon, Stewart, McNamara). 1965 (Box 247, Folder 5)
    - Oversized Materials: Photographs and Posters, Photograph Cabinet Meeting. February1965 (Box 247, Folder 6)
    - Oversized Materials: Photographs and Posters, Poster “The Quiet Crisis,” by Mauldin, Chicago Sun Times. 1963 (Box 247, Folder 7)
    - Oversized Materials: Photographs and Posters, Poster “Dirty Old Man River,” by Reg Manning. March 1966 (Box 247, Folder 8)
    - Oversized Materials: Photographs and Posters, Poster from the Bureau of Fisheries and Wildlife. (Box 247, Folder 9)
    - Oversized Materials: Photographs and Posters, Photograph Mount Kilimanjaro Climb. September 1963 (Box 247, Folder 10)
    - Oversized Materials: Photographs and Posters, Two Photographs-Theodore Roosevelt and John Muir at Yosemite and Stewart Udall and John F. Kennedy at Yosemite. 1905-1906, August 1961 (Box 247, Folder 11)
  - Scrapbooks, 1920-1969
    The scrapbooks are arranged by size and date. The following items recent additions in 2002. Additional scrapbooks are located throughout the the entire collection.
    - Scrapbooks, 1920-1946 (Box 248)
      World Warr II; Basketball, 1920-1946
      Mormon Mission; 1940-42, 1960-61
    - Scrapbooks, 1950-1963 (Box 249)
      Arizona Congress, 1950s (bulk 1956)
      Shooting the Wild Colorado February 1963
    - Scrapbooks, 1960s (Box 250)
      LBJ Years, 1963-1969
      LBJ Years, White House Meetings and events, 1963-1969
      Stewart Udall and Lady Bird's Activities, Washington DC, Potomac Rebeautification process, inscriptions by Lady Bird, 1960s